



Specialties

- > UI/UX Design
- > Interaction Design
- > Project Management
- > Story Boarding
- > Style Boarding
- > Prototyping
- > Graphic Design
- > SVG Icons
- > Illustration
- > Typography

Tools

- > Sketch
- > Adobe Creative Suite
- > Affinity Creative Suite
- > NPM/WebPack
- > HTML
- > CSS, SASS, Flexbox, Grid
- > Bootstrap
- > JavaScript
- > Vue.js, Nuxt.js
- > Gridsome

₽ Profile

Graphic Design/Art Director in Miami. Moved to London, England and worked at top ten Ad agency TBWA (Omnicom). Early 2000s transitioned to UI/UX Design.

Guru-level with Adobe CS, including InDesign, Sketch, InVision, Axure, APPinity Suite, Bootstrap. Love reducing complexity to elegance. When designed well, the UI seems inevitable. Learned HTML/CSS to own design, JavaScript a little thin.

Experience

> 2017 - present

Contracting, ValentinaDesign.com, DrewHarper.com, Dollar General Mockup, continuous learning of JavaScript, Vue.js, Nuxt, Gridsome.

> UI/UX Designer, TN Dept of Education

Contract, Nashville, TN, 12/2016-06/2017

> UI/UX Designer, Civic Inc.

Contract, Nashville, TN, 09/2013 - 02/2015

> UI/UX Designer, JPay.com

Full-time, Miami, FL, 2008-2013

Many projects, basically a one-man Web Dev department

- > JPay.com, Mobile App, Phablet App B2C
- > MLotto Project App & Website

> UI/UX Designer, Safari Ltd.

Contract, Miami, FL, 2007-2008

> UI/UX Designer, Planning Grp Int. – now Sapient Nitro Contract, Miami, FL, 2006

> UI/UX Designer, Diaz & Cooper Adv.

Full-time, Miami, FL, 2003-2006

> Art Director & Web Designer, TBWA

Full-time, London UK, 1998 - 2000

Education

- > International Fine Arts College, 1987, Miami, FL, Commercial Art, AA Degree
- > Trent College, 1984, Long Eaton, UK

 Boarding school in England, received Art

 Scholarship. Played Rugby For my county.

Referrals

- > Don Pham Project Manager don.kim.pham@gmail.com (954) 801-9975
- Mike Mack Coder mikemack88@gmail.com (415) 509-1909
- > Joanna Perry Creative Director joanna@nomadhome.net +44 788-418-7100